A Guide to the Photographic Negatives of Richard N. Anderson,
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Photographic Negatives of Richard N. Anderson
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
5793 -a through -k
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given in ten groupings to the Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library by Richard N. Anderson, 4505 N. Kings Highway, B-7, P.O. box 7740, Myrtle Beach, S. C. 29577. The first collection 5793-a of 397 items was given on April 11, 1980; the second collection 5793-b of 17 items was given on December 12, 1980; the third collection 5793-c of 36 items was given on August 25, 1983; the fourth collection 5793-d of 618 items was given on December 19, 1983; the fifth collection 5793-e of 247 items was given on February 23, 1984; the sixth collection 5793-f of 409 items was given on May 8, 1984 the seventh collection 5793-g of 230 items was given on June 11, 1984; the eighth collection 5793-h of 282 items was given on September 12, 1984; the ninth collection 5793-i,-j of 605 items was given on July 30, 1986 and July 12, 1988; the tenth collection 5793-k of 6 items was given on February 14, 1991.
Scope and Content
This collection is ca. 2,733 items, 2 Hollinger boxes, 1 linear foot, and contains photographs and contact sheets by Richard N. Anderson of historic buildings, houses, churches, bridges, airports, railroads, businesses, politicians and political events, including the civil rights movement.
The images are from the District of Columbia, Charlottesville, Lexington, Petersburg, Williamsburg, and Richmond, Virginia from 1940 to 1972. There are also some images from Hurricane Hazel in Canada, a fire in Harlem, New York, 1937 and a building in San Francisco, California.
The images from the civil rights movement include Martin Luther King, the Poor People's March, Virginia Union University Freedom March, Black Integration Lunch Counter Sit-ins, and an arrest of protestors in front of the Thalhimer's department store in Richmond, Virginia.
There are also images of the Miss Virginia Beauty Pageant; the Tobacco Bowl football game; the Byrd Airport dedication; a concert in Cabell Hall at the University of Virginia; a Davis Cup Tennis Tournament in Richmond, Virginia; a visit by Indira Gandhi to Williamsburg, Virginia; ICBM missiles at Dahlgren, Virginia; nuclear cruises; views of Petersburg, Virginia; the Press Club of Virginia; the press corps during a speech by President Harry S. Truman at Monticello; railroad yards; views of Richmond; an engraving of Hore Browse Trist; a garden at the University of Virginia; and WRVA radio station during 1960 and 1965 Virginia elections coverage.
Politicians, entertainers and other significant leaders in the collection include: Governor James Lindsay Almond, Virginia Senator Howard Anderson, William Battle, Senator Stuart D. Baker, Francis Biddle, Bill Robinson, Harry Flood Byrd Jr., Harry Flood Byrd Sr., Admiral Richard E. Byrd, Dan Daniel, Governor Colgate Darden, Clifford Dowdey, William Dudley, President Dwight D. Eisenhower, Senator [Allen Joseph] Ellender, Indira Gandhi, Governor Mills E. Godwin, Senator Barry Goldwater, Arthur Godfrey, [Benny Goodman Orchestra,] Fleet Admiral William F. Halsey, Governor Albertis S. Harrison, Jr., Governor Linwood Holton, Vice President Hubert and Muriel Humphrey, President Lyndon B. Johnson, Martin Luther King, Judge Robert Mehridge, John Lloyd Newcomb, President Richard M. Nixon, President Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Charlie Spivak and his orchestra, Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., Governor William Tuck, George Wallace, General and Mrs. Edwin Watson, and L. Douglas Wilder.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically by the names of individuals and topical headings.
Contents List
- Governor James Lindsay Almond; Football game, n.d. [1950; 1958; 1959], 79 images, 1 photograph, 6 negatives. (Box-folder 1:1)
  43 images and 1 photograph of Governor Almond at [press conferences] #1460A1-3; B1-4; F1-4; G1-5; #1122 A-H, #1123 A-C, #1784-E-F, #35-178 G-H; [football game]; 3 images of the Governor's office handing out the School Cross Bulletin #1460 E5-7; 2 images of [Norfolk police serving a school resolution on Dodson] #1460 H1-2; 2 images of the Norfolk School petition UPI 1958 Oct #1460 I1-2; 8 images of Governor Almond giving an address at the Virginia Education Association #1460 J1-4, K1-4; 6 images of Governor Almond meeting with the Warren County School Board #1784, #1124 A-B; 8 images of Governor Almond's [televised State address on school integration] 1959 Jan. 20 #1125-A-H; 6 negatives of Governor Almond #1784 A-F; 8 images of the Governor James Lindsay Almond and the Tobacco Bowl Queen, and the football game #1460 AP 1-8.
- American Independent Party Convention, n. d., 11 images. (Box-folder 1:2)
  #35-201.
- [Ammonia explosion at Merchant's Cold Storage Warehouse, Richmond, Virginia 1958 January 16;] car crash, and a brewery explosion and fire in Harlem, New York, [1937], 12 images. (Box-folder 1:3)
  9 images of an explosion at Merchant's Cold Storage Warehouse, Richmond, Virginia #1432 A-F, H-K; 1 image of a car crash #1432-G; 1 image of a brewery explosion and fire in Harlem, New York #N45-1432.
- Stuart D. Baker senatorial campaign, n. d., 3 images. (Box-folder 1:4)
  #1460 AJ1-3.
- William Battle at a press conference 1969; Senators at the Virginia General Assembly, 1972, 18 images. (Box-folder 1:5)
  12 images of Governor William Battle #35-202 AF-AH; 6 images of the State Senators Howard Anderson and L. Douglas Wilder at the Virginia General Assembly #35-202 AI.
- Harry Flood Byrd, Jr. giving an address, 1970, 34 images. (Box-folder 1:6)
  #35-200 BW-CB.
- Byrd Airport, Richmond, Virginia, [1955-1960], 14 images and 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:7)
  10 images of the Byrd Airport #1129 A-J; 1 photograph of Byrd Airport at the time of dedication #1508 A; 4 images of [Byrd Airport] when bad weather diverts several airplanes #1508 A.
- Byrd Airport [dedication] with [Arthur Godfrey and Richard E. Byrd], n.d., 11 images. (Box-folder 1:8)
  #1460 AO 1-11.
- Cabell Hall Concert, 1940, 2 images, 4 photographs. (Box-folder 1:9)
  4 photographs of a concert in Cabell Hall #1835 A-D; 2 images of [Tony Pastor] singing at Cabell Hall and greeting at the train #1460 BD 1-2.
- Capitol Building, Richmond, Virginia, 1963, 86 images, 1 transparency, 1 photograph #1179-B. (Box-folder 1:10)
  9 images and 1 photograph of the Capitol Square, the Life of Virginia Building, and the Hotel Richmond 1179 A-H; #1128; 30 images of the interior of the Capitol #35-178 D1-6; 34 images of the renovations of the Capitol #35-178 I 1-6; 8 images of the Bell Tower at Capitol Square and the ground-breaking ceremony for the new City Hall #35-202 AX-AY; 4 images and one transparency of the State Capitol subsequent to the installation of the second flagpole; Christmas tree on the portico #1503A-D.
- Civic Center, Norfolk Virginia, n.d., 29 images. (Box-folder 1:11)
  #35-178 K 2-6.
- Civil Rights Movement, Martin Luther King, Sit-Ins, Arrests, Marches, Ku Klux Klan Rallies; Yale School of Architecture 1963 June 15; 1965; 1967; n. d., 206 images, 15 photographs, 37 photocopies. (Box-folder 1:12)
  6 photographs of Martin Luther King and other activists; CF; 2 photographs (and 1 duplicate) of the Black Integration lunch counter sit-in at Woolworth's (n. d.) #35-200 CC-CD; 1 photograph of protestors in front of Thalhimers Department Store and 18 images of the Civil Rights lunch counter sit-ins and protests (n. d.) #35-200 CC-CE; 1 photograph of the Virginia Union University Freedom March (n. d.) #35-200 DB; 17 images of the Civil rights sit-ins and protests #35-202 AQ-AS; 28 images of the Civil Rights protests [D. C. March 1963] #35-201 P-T; 2 images of the D.C. March [Poor People's March 1963] #35-200 CF; 24 images of the Ku Klux Klan rallies (1965) #35-200 CG-CK; 25 images of the Ku Klux Klan rallies (1967) #35-200 CL-CN; 23 images and 2 photographs of the [Poor People's March or D. C. March 1963] #35-200 CO-CT; 54 images of Virginia Union University Freedom March (n. d.) #35-200 CU-DC; 12 images of the Yale School of Architecture #35-200 DD-DH; 11 images (photocopy) of Poor people's March [D.C. March].
  2 oversize photographs of the lunch counter sit-in at Woolworth's and the Virginia Union Freedom March; #35-200 CD; #35-200 CZ.
- Colgate Darden, John Lloyd Newcomb, and Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., [1940], 8 images, 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:13)
  1 photograph of Colgate Darden and John Lloyd Newcomb at the theatre #1460 BE; 2 images of Edward R. Stettinius, Jr. and [Admiral William F. Halsey] at the Farmington Country Club #1460 BF.1-2; 2 images of Edward R. Stettinius, Jr., and [John Lloyd Newcomb] #1460 BH.1-2; 2 images of Edward Stettinius, Jr. and [Colgate Darden] at the University of Virginia #1460 BG.1-2; 2 images of John Lloyd Newcomb and [Francis Biddle?] at the University of Virginia [1940] #1460 BI.1-BI.2.
- Davis Cup Tennis Tournament; Sculpture of the Governor by Jan Hochman, n.d., 78 images on 4 contact sheets. (Box-folder 1:14)
  47 images of the Davis Cup Tennis Tournament #35-202 BE-BL; 31 images of Jan Hochman's sculpture of the Governor #35-202 BM-BR.
- Clifford Dowdey and family, [1950], 4 images. (Box-folder 1:15)
  #35-201 G.
- Dwight D. Eisenhower at the Virginia Capitol, 1965 September 14, 12 images. (Box-folder 1:16)
  #35-178 A.
- Indira Gandhi at Williamsburg, Virginia 1965; Indian Annual Thanksgiving Tribute, 1966, 31 images, 3 negatives. (Box-folder 1:17)
  16 images of Indira Gandhi in Williamsburg #35-200 BJ-BK, #35-217 A-B; 15 images of the Indians Annual Thanksgiving Tribute #35-217 C-D, #1542 G-I, 1784 G-I; 3 negatives of Indians with a Thanksgiving gift for Governor Tuck #1784 G-I.
- Governor Mills E. Godwin and the General Assembly of Virginia 1962 January 9; 1964 Jan 30; 1968, 1969, [1969 September 12] 1970; 1972; Governor Mills E. Godwin wins AAA award of merit 1968; General Assembly Sessions; Inauguration of Governor Mills E. Godwin 1966; Governor Mills E. Godwin and Eugene McCarthy; Mrs. Lyndon Johnson at the Governor's Mansion [1969 September 12] Press Conference; European Trade Mission, n. d., 278 images. (Box-folder 1:18)
  29 images of Governor Mills E. Godwin's inauguration and parade #35-200 H-N; 19 images of Governor Mills E. Godwin's press conference #35-200 O-R; 12 images of Mrs. Lyndon Johnson at the Governor's mansion (1969) #35-200 V-W; 10 images of Governor Mills E. Godwin and Eugene McCarthy (1969) #35-200 X-Y; 11 images of Mills E. Godwin News Conference (1970) #35-201 AN-AO; 5 images of Mills E. Godwin receiving AAA awards of merit 1968; #35-202 A; 10 images of the General Assembly in Williamsburg #35-202 B-C; 3 images of legislators (1964) #35-178 A.3; 24 images of the General Assembly Commemorative Session in Williamsburg, Virginia 1968 February 3 #35-202 D-G; 35 images of the Virginia Constitutional Revision Commission Wren Building, Williamsburg, Virginia #35-202 H-M; 6 images of Bill Dudley at the General Assembly 1972 February #35-202 N; 16 images of the General Assembly Opening Session 1972 February #35-202O-Q; 10 images of the General Assembly and exterior of State Capitol #35-202 R-S; 52 images of the General Assembly Special Session 1963 November including 5 images of an unidentified woman with her dog and playing cards #35-202 T-AB; 6 images of Budget Hearings 1962 Jan 6 #35-201 U; 10 images of the Democratic Caucus-Virginia Capitol 1962 January 9 #35-178 I; 27 images of the Virginia General Assembly 1964 #35-178 C.1-6; 64 images of the Virginia General Assembly 1964 January 30 #38-178 B.1-6, #35-178 H.2-6; 42 images of the Virginia General Assembly 1969 #35-201 V-AA; 36 images of the Virginia General Assembly Opening 1970 #35-201 AH-AM; 23 images of the Virginia General Assembly 1972 March #35-201 AP-AT;14 images of Dan Daniel at the General Assembly #35-202 AC-AE; 4 images of the Governor's office handing out School Crossing Bulletin; 21 images of the European Trade Mission 1970 #35-200 AC-AF.
- Barry Goldwater at a 1960 Republican Rally, n. d., 7 images. (Box-folder 1:19)
  #1541 A-G.
- Benny Goodman Orchestra, n. d., 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:19)
- Fleet Admiral William F. Halsey, Jr, USN, n. d., 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:20)
  1 photograph of Fleet Admiral F. Halsey, Jr. at the University of Virginia after World War II #1460 BC.
- Albertis S. Harrison, Inauguration, 1962 January 13, 91 images. (Box-folder 1:21)
  35-178 E.1-6, F.1-6, G.1-4.
- Heart Transplant patient and Nazi Art, n. d., 16 images. (Box-folder 1:22)
  6 images of a heart transplant patient #35-200 DM; 10 images of Nazi Art #35-200 DN-DO.
- Governor Linwood Holton Inauguration with James Lindsay Almond and Harry Byrd Sr. present, 1970, 64 images. (Box-folder 1:23)
  35 images of the inauguration of Governor Linwood Holton #35-201 AB-AG; 17 images of a press conference with Governor Linwood Holton #35-200 S-U; 2 images of James Lindsay Almond #35-200 AA-AB; 10 images of Governor Linwood Holton and Harry Flood Byrd, Sr., #35-200 Z.
- Mr. and Mrs. Hubert Humphrey 1961; 1965-1968, n. d., 42 images. (Box-folder 1:24)
  21 images of Mrs. Muriel Humphrey at the Governor's Mansion 1961 #35-200 BE-BI; 18 images of a Speech by Vice President Hubert H. Humphrey with Governor Mills E. Godwin #35-200 BS-BU; 3 images of the Young Democrats Club Meeting #35-200 BV.
- [Hurricane Hazel], n. d., 3 images. (Box-folder 1:25)
  3 images of damage from a hurricane in Canada 1954 Oct. 15, 16 #1460 AM1-3
- ICBM [Intercontinental Ballistic Missiles] at Dahlgren, Virginia (missile address), [1955], 2 photographs. (Box-folder 1:26)
  [1955] #N45-1428.
- Lyndon B. Johnson 1960; Senator [Allen Joseph] Ellender, n. d., 37 images. (Box-folder 1:27)
  18 images of Lyndon B. Johnson during the Kennedy Johnson Presidential campaign 1960 #35-200 AG-AI; 10 images of Lyndon B. Johnson at the Arena #35-200 AJ-AK; 9 images of Senator [Allen Joseph] Ellender of Louisiana #35-200 AL-AM.
- Judge Robert R. Mehridge, Jr.; Old U.S. State Department Building, 1968; 1972 January 11, 18, 36 images. (Box-folder 1:28)
  4 images of the old U.S. State Department Building, Washington, D. C. [1968] #35-202 AJ; 15 images of Judge Robert R. Mehridge, Jr. 1972 January 18 #35-202 AK-AM; 17 images of the home of Judge Robert R. Mehridge, Jr. with guards, 1972 January 11 #35-202 AN-AP.
- Paul G. McIntire photocopy of a photograph, n. d., 1 item. (Box-folder 1:28)
- Miscellaneous oversize negatives, n. d., 566 images.
  Images of [the Richmond Byrd Airport]; football game; fireworks above [Richmond] skyline; train station; General Assembly; James River and view of Richmond; Queen of Tobacco Bowl; basketball game; zoo; St. Mathews Lutheran Church; River Park; Richmond Industrial Loan & Thrift; Martin Luther King; [Lee] Statue; women building a snowman; Richmond three level overpass.
- Naval Reserve Cruise to Haiti, 1950, 12 images. (Box-folder 1:29)
  1950 #1428 A-L.
- Richard Nixon on a campaign trip to Richmond, 1968 January, 14 images of the WRVA Kennedy/Nixon election coverage 1968 January #35-200 BB-BD. (Box-folder 1:30)
- Nuclear Cruiser USS Long Beach; Nuclear Carrier USS Enterprise at Hampton Roads; Views of Appomatox, 1962 April 10, 23 images. (Box-folder 1:31)
  11 images of views of Appomattox #35-202 AT-AU; 12 images of the Nuclear Cruiser USS Long Beach, Nuclear Carrier USS Enterprise at Hampton Roads, Va. 1962 April. #35-202 AV-AW.
- Petersburg, Virginia, Jamestown, Virginia and other places, n.d.; 1957, 32 images, 2 photographs. (Box-folder 1:32)
  4 images of the Jamestown Exposition Park [1957] #1460 AV.1-4; 1 photograph of the Norfolk & Western Railroad yards, Roanoke Virginia [1948] #1460 AW; 2 images of the Petersburg Leather Handle Factory #1460 AX.1-2; 12 images of the Pratt Clinic, Petersburg, Virginia [1956] #1460 AY.1-12; 10 images of the Crippled Children's Hospital, Richmond, Virginia [1938-9] #1460 L.1-8, [1958 Sept. 10] C.1-2; 4 images of quadruplets in incubators at the hospital [1958 October] #1460 K.1-4.
- [Political Debate;] House Fire and Automobile Wreck 1968 February 10, n. d., 34 images. (Box-folder 1:33)
  28 images of a debate [with Garroway, Price, Jessel, Gregory, Sahl, Jenkins, Telford, and Hudson] #35-202 BS-BW; 6 images of a house fire and auto wreck [1968 February 10] #35-202 BX-BY.
- Press Club of Virginia, n. d., 6 images. (Box-folder 1:34)
  #1542 A-F.
- Press corps during Harry Truman speech at Monticello, 1940 July 4, 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:35)
  #1429.
- Railroad, News clipping photographs about Richmond's Railroad crossings and the Aluminum Convention Hall Dome, n. d., 4 items, 5 images. (Box-folder 1:36)
  3 photocopies of photographs of the three-level crossing upgrading to a fourth level; 2 photocopies of photographs of the Aluminum Convention Hall Dome.
- Railroad Yards at Richmond, Virginia, n. d., 45 images, 7 photographs, 11 negatives. (Box-folder 1:37)
  3 images of the Seaboard Railroad Office Building under construction [1958] #1460 U.1-3; 32 images of Railroads [in Richmond] including [a dedication of] a three level overpass and a nineteenth century [wood-burning] locomotive #35-200 A-G; 8 images of the three level railroad, Richmond, Virginia 1958 October 12 #1131 A-H; 1 image of the Norfolk and Western locomotive 374 Richmond, Virginia #1132; 14 images, 4 photographs of a railroad and a three level overpass, Richmond, Virginia n.d. #1784; 2 images of the Triple Crossing, Richmond, Virginia 1956-1957 winter, looking southeast along the Southern Ry track, at ground level. A Seaboard Air Line Ry southbound passenger train passing under the C&O viaduct. A train headed by a E7A diesel loco 3047 and another loco, probably E6A. Only cars visible are a Pennsylvania RR express refrigerator car and a Seaboard dormitory baggage car 6050 [1955] #1393A-B; 2 images of the Triple Crossing, Richmond, Virginia 1956-1957 winter, looking southeast, viewed from a highly elevated location north of C&O viaduct. Northbound Seaboard Air Line Ry train has just passed under viaduct, and its caboose is still partly in its shadow [1955] #1393 C-D; 1 photograph of the Seaboard Air Line Ry passenger train, southbound, headed by three diesel locals, just south of Richmond, Virginia with city skyline in background. Front ¾ view in the mid distance of a long train on straight track, about 16 cars, mixed heavy and light weight #1394-B; 1 photograph of the Atlantic Coast Line RR Cowardin Ave. Yard, looking north from Cowardin Ave. overpass with city skyline in background and a few box cars in the foreground Winter [1940's or 1950's] #1394-E; 1 photograph of the Main Street Station, Richmond, Virginia, winter [1940], looking south from Marshall Street viaduct, from point midway between C&O Ry and Seaboard Air Line Ry tracks, Freight train (mostly boxcars) on C&O Ry track. #1394-F; 1 photograph of the Southern Ry Belle Isle Yard, Richmond, Virginia [1940's] from the south end of the Lee Bridge, with the James River and the city skyline in the background. #1394-G; 11 negatives of Railroad yards #1785 A-L.
- Richmond, Virginia Aerial views, construction, bridges, concrete construction, n. d., 56 images, 7 photographs. (Box-folder 1:38)
  5 photographs with aerial views of Richmond #1532-A, E-H; 7 images of aerial views including the Colonial Theater on the corner of 8th and Broad Street Road and the Federal Building #1507A-D, #1532 B-D; 17 images of bridges, including some skyline views from Riverside Drive on the south side of the James River showing the Lee Bridge and Tredegar Iron Works #1504 A-B, 1460 AH.1-15; 3 images of the earliest construction of a concrete bridge in Virginia #1502 A-C; 2 images of the bridge at the ACCA railroad yard with a joke sign on it falsely identifying it as the Rappahanock River Bridge #1511 A-B.
- Richmond, Virginia. Banks, n. d., 8 images. (Box-folder 1:39)
  8 images of various banks including the Central National Bank, and Security Federal Savings #1525 A-F, [1956] #1460 S.1-2.
- Richmond, Virginia, Businesses and Hotels Folder, n. d., 184 images, 3 photographs and 2 negatives. (Box-folder 1:40)
  5 images of the William Byrd Motor Hotel; (Hotel William Byrd) #1523A-C, [1954 March] #1460 P.1-2; 2 images of the Hotel Jefferson [1955] #1460 AG.1-2; 14 images of the [Martha Kay Motel] #1460 T.1-16; 6 images of the Life of Virginia building #1506 A-B, #35-178 K; 2 images of Bourne-Jones Motor Company [1940's] #1460 AI.1-2; 1 photograph of the Moore Building with other store fronts such as New Amsterdam/United States Casualty Company, Sutton & Company, Realtors, R.B. Chaffin & Co. Realtors, Richmond Bakery Workers Health & Welfare Insurance Office #1530; 2 images of Richmond Food Stores warehouse and administrative offices [1950] #1514 A-B; 1 photograph of the Rish [Farm] Equipment Company #1513; 7 images of the River Road Shopping Center at Huguenot; Thalhimers, River Road Pharmacy, Berry Burke Company and the Colony Shop #1517 A-G; 8 images of Siegel's Supermarket [1950] #1510 A-H; 4 images of Stein's Clothiers, National, State, and Colonial Theaters #1505 A-D; 4 images of Thalhimers Department Store #1516 A-D; 7 images of downtown businesses including the Oldest Music House in Virginia, Morton's, Lowe's Opticians, McCrorys [five and dime store], Cargill & Wilson Advertising Agency #1528 B, Mark Monroe Motor Hotel, Avis Rent-a-Car, The Straus Company, J. D. Carneal & Sons Inc. Realtors #1528 A-G; 2 images of Sargeant's Dog Care Products Building #1515 A-B; 8 images of the offices of The Colonial Group #1519 A-H; 2 images of the Offices of Dun & Bradstreet at 514 Willow Lawn Drive #1521 A-B; 16 images of the United States Fidelity & Guarantee Insurance Company #1520 A-P; 7 images of the Joint Airlines City Ticket Office #1460 Q.1-7, [Cafeteria?] #1529 A; Office #1529 B-D; Model for a building #1529 E; Travel Agency #1529 F-K; Medical College of Virginia #1529 L; 1 photograph of the construction of Jenkins Book Mgf. Co. Warehouse adjoining Broad Street Station; [One of the earliest concrete buildings in Virginia 1950] #1512 A-U; 6 images of an English double-decker bus at 9th and Grace Street, 1965 #38-178 A.5; 2 images of [legislators Hodges, Harrison, Collins and Elington] 1964 July 7 #35-178 A.6; 10 images of Richmond buildings #35-178 J.4-6; 1 image of the Richmond skyline #1127; 1 image of the Reynolds Metal Company Building #1130; 18 images of Main Street [1967] #35-202 AZ-BB; 4 images of the Richmond-Petersburg Turnpike under construction #1460 V.1-4; 7 images of the Virginia Inn under construction #35-202 BC-BD; 1 negative of the Mosque and 1 negative of the American Building.
- Richmond, Virginia, Churches, n. d., 36 images, 1 photograph. (Box-folder 1:41)
  2 images of the Bethany Place Baptist Church #1526 I-J; 8 images of the Christian Science Reading Room #1460 M.1-6, #1526 R-S; 1 image of the First Church of Christ Scientist #1526 Q; 1 photograph of Ginter Park Methodist Church #1460AF; 6 images of the interior of Ginter Park Methodist Church [1955] #35-178 A.4; 1 image of the Methodist Building #1526 W; 1 photograph of an architect's rendering of the River Road Methodist Church #1526; 8 images of the River Road Methodist Church #1526A-H; 6 images of an unidentified church #1526K-P; 1 image of an unidentified church #1526 T; 3 images of an unidentified church #1526 U-V, All Saints Church #1526 X; 1 photograph of an unidentified church [1957] #1460 AD.
- Richmond, Virginia. Government Office Buildings, n. d., 31 images, 8 negatives. (Box-folder 1:42)